shopfort1.com 2008-06-17

# ShopforT1.com Privacy Policy

|  |   
**Registration**

* * *

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the quote request form. This information is required to generate a real-time T1 quote for you. The information that we gather comprises of your name, your business name, your installation phone number, your contact phone number, your email address, and the physical installation address of the T1 line in question. This information is used by certified ShopforT1 consultants to both contact you and to assist you with the decision-making process, outlining the strengths and weaknesses of each carrier that appears in your real-time quote. If you do not wish to be contacted, you can make your wishes known on Step 2 of the quote request form (Select the "Window Shopper" option in the contact preference section). 

You will have the option to provide optional contact information (such as cell phone number, additional contact numbers, and comments about your situation) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

Once you submit your information, you will receive an email thanking you for your quote request. This email will contain a link that will make it possible for you to view your quote at a later time and/or request additional contact from members of our sales team. No additional email correspondences will be sent to you once you receive the initial "Thank You" message. 

Telarus, Inc. is the sole owner of ShopforT1.com. Telarus, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Telarus, Inc. does supplement the data it collects with additional data received from third party sources - such as address validation from the USPS, phone number/zip code matching, and email address pre-screening. 

**TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program**

* * *

Telarus, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.ShopforT1.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Patrick Oborn at poborn@telarus.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should [contact TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) who will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Orders**

* * *

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and physical address). Financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date) is NOT required to purchase services, as that will take place later through written (hard-copy) credit approval forms. 

We use the information we collect on the order form to fulfill your orders. Before we submit any order to a carrier, we will use this information to contact you so that we can make sure your paperwork is completed accurately. 

Telarus, Inc. will not transmit your information to any of our telecom partners until you are ready to sign paperwork and enter into a service contract. The only information that may be transmitted to our telecom partners prior to you signing paperwork is your address and installation phone number which is used solely for quoting purposes. This information will not be shared, sold, rented, or traded with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

**Email / Phone Solicitation**

* * *

Telarus, Inc., ShopForT1.com or its business partners will communicate with you according to the Contact Preference you enter in Step 2 of our online quoting process. The contact methods include email and phone solicitation. These communications are for the intended benefit of our visitors and do not come with any commitment to buy anything from ShopforT1.com. 

In the welcome letter that you will receive from ShopforT1.com when you create your first quote you will see an "unsubscribe" link at the bottom which will allow you to opt-out of any future communications with ShopforT1.com and our partners. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

* * *

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing the Sales Rep (their contact information is found on the "Thank You" email you received when you generated your first quote) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

Telarus, Inc.  
12401 S. 450 E. Suite D1  
Draper, UT 84020  
(801) 523-2100 

**Cookies**

* * *

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

We set a persistent cookie to track the referring web site so that we may adequately track your quotes and compensate the appropriate affiliate partner who originally brought you to our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site without any change to your user experience. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by ShopforT1.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Testimonials**

* * *

If you post a testimonial on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this site, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in a testimonial. **Bulletin Boards**

* * *

If you post in our forum on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. **Additional Disclosures**

* * *

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at poborn@telarus.com. 

**Agent Confidentiality**

* * *

Telarus, Inc. holds in highest confidence all information that our agents submit to us. This information allows Telarus, Inc. to properly pay commissions and to monitor the use of the private Telarus Agent Back Office. This confidentiality pledge does NOT protect the privacy of competing organizations that have set up "dummy" agent accounts in order to scout our back office and engage in any other illegal and/or unethical conduct. Telarus, Inc. reserves the right to publish any information submitted to our databases by such organizations, which may subject them to public humiliation and legal damages. **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

* * *

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
